What is the role of the company in the future?
For those of you who are experienced in the field,
I would like to introduce some of our projects.
In the past few years,
our company has been working on
high-end material models
in the field of 3D printing.
These two projects are currently in development,
including a few years ago in Hong Kong,
as well as a few years ago
in China.
Since then,
our company has been working on
high-end material models
in the field of 3D printing.
Next, I would like to introduce these models.
First of all,
I would like to introduce two models
based on the needs of different projects
and their performance.
The first model is the Geometry Cache,
and the second model is the Time Simulation.
Let's first look at the Geometry Cache.
The Geometry Cache is a tool
that can be used for
high-end materials.
For example,
we have seen a lot of
high-end materials such as steel shavings
and other things
that we often see in our MD projects.
For example,
there are some high-end materials
on the windows,
or some high-end materials
on the sculptures.
In fact,
I find that this MD
has already made a decision
when designing,
and it is a very good model.
In fact,
it can be used for
many other projects,
including the
Geometry Cache.
It is a very good model
for many other projects,
such as
the Geometry Cache.
The Geometry Cache
is a very good model
for the production of
high-end materials
such as
art,
and media.
The Geometry Cache
is a great model
for all kinds of
high-end materials,
and it is very good
for introducing
the new
high-end materials
to our project.
The Geometry Cache
is a very good model
We can also use this kind of dynamic system to study the ROD.
And then we can also use it in MDP to work with the ROD to simulate EVE.
In the end, we can also use it in the game engine.
We can see that this Maximo network is familiar to everyone.
Especially with the current AI processes.
Maximo is similar to iCom.
It has a lot of animals on it.
This network allows us to prepare a lot of animations that can be used to test materials in the MDP network.
Or some performance animations.
At the same time, this network is also very suitable for animations in Unreal.
Whether it's in Unreal 4 or Unreal 5.
An animation of a white man or a baby with a sense of texture.
Through these animations.
Through
Maximo's Converter.
This can be downloaded directly from the YouTube.
And then it can directly import the ROD.
And then generate such animations.
And then you can use it directly in the game.
Of course, if we don't use this software.
We can use the message reset function directly.
The new version of 5.3 and 5.4.5.
The reset function has been done very well.
We can see that the same is the human action.
And the animation between the Skyrim and the ROD that we are going to use.
We can use it to change the work.
And then check whether it matches the effect.
And then because today we are mainly talking about a real activity.
So here I am using Maximo's Converter as an example.
To explain such a process.
So today in the morning.
Including before.
Sherry has already talked about.
Maybe in the new version of MDP.
There is already a function like that.
And then in the future.
We will directly use Maximo's Converter.
To complete the performance of this action.
The transition.
From the initial action.
From the hitbox.
Or from the standby action.
Or from the t-box.
We have an animal in an animation.
Such a transition.
We need to use this.
Baitment.
Baitment control rig.
To complete it.
So through.
Before our initial point.
For example.
From the first point.
It is the start of our entire animation transition.
So we will move forward.
From 20 to 30 points.
So in fact.
Because most of the action in the animation.
Every second is 32 points.
So we are almost.
Between 20 to 30 points.
It is the transition.
It is almost.
So we can follow our action.
To see.
Our.
Idea of the animation.
And then.
After the Baitment control.
We can see.
In this transition.
There are a lot of references.
So these transition references.
In fact.
It is based on.
The performance of this.
This initial.
A force.
To the initial force of our animation.
In the middle.
This transition.
So we delete these references.
After that.
We can quickly make a transition animation.
So when the animation is ready.
After the animation is ready.
Next.
We need.
In 2024.
The newly released.
The.
This.
aliasing.
Is very helpful.
We are in.
Through this software.
With the nanobot.
You can directly download this.
The interface.
So we know.
We have already taken.
We require.
The animation.
When we download.
Google.
We need to take the.
Hand.
The head.
Body.
The legs.
The other.
People.
After downloading this, we can download it with one click.
This is very effective.
After downloading this official plugin,
we also need to give a plugin called SubstancePainter,
including its IHI, which is called DerivS11.
Currently, DerivS12 is still available in some languages.
The second thing is that we still need to start the semi-transparent cache function.
In the case of liuSync,
we only need to point to one of our played animations.
Then, through this animation, through this Spanish button,
one click can lead to our MD.
In the process of leading to MD, we need to pay attention to a few things.
First, we need to ensure that the CLO of MD,
the liuSync interface, must be turned on.
We can't turn it off.
Second, we need to ensure that our entire animation
in MD cannot be turned off.
Third, we can't turn it off.
Fourth, we can't turn it off.
Fifth, we can't turn it off.
In the process of leading to MD,
there is one more problem that we need to pay attention to.
We can see that the person here is complete,
but in fact, many of my colleagues often ask me
why I am leading to MD as a whiteboard,
or why I am leading to MD as our CLO.
We see that the preview image here
can only be viewed in one language.
In fact, all the components of our leading to MD
can only be seen here,
including the head, body, and feet.
Even some of the avatars that we have prepared,
it has some hair,
and I am leading to MD as well.
It will also lead to MD through the sync interface,
and it is convenient for us to do the settlement.
After completing these assets,
we will lead to MD,
and we will start to do the settlement
with the tools we have prepared.
In this process, I have chosen four sets of clothes,
and there is a storage group,
and then,
as you can see,
it is connected to the Internet,
and it is even more convenient for us to see our clients.
There are also clothes that are
made of a certain type of material,
such as a cotton or a silk fabric.
There are also clothes that are made of a certain type of material,
As you can see,
it is easily accessible to everyone.
So, we will see that for you.
I would like to talk about the process of
leading the MD to MD,
I think in the new version, there is a very good feature of self-sufficiency.
Because it will be able to provide us with a lot of the assets we used to have,
such as clothes and fast food, which is very useful in the new version.
We know that in fact,
the NB-based Arata may have a relatively high height,
and the MetaTorrent application will be higher than that of the high-end.
And their standard postage and their labor schedule are also different.
So at this time, the function of self-sufficiency is very convenient.
There is also a small difference when doing this set.
At the beginning, I forgot to use the chest buckle to fix the chest buckle.
But now, in the analysis process, I found that
in fact, I think the problem of sound and sound isolation is a relatively good form of expression.
That is to say, when the finger is turning,
when the finger is turning,
the sound is not as clear as the sound.
The sound is not as clear as the sound.
That is to say,
when the finger is turning,
and the hand is turning,
the sound is not as clear as the sound.
So I think this is actually an extra one-off after all.
So I think the deep thing is still being preserved.
And it shows that during the analysis process in NB,
the height is a flexibility and accuracy.
So after this, we will start with the regarding of the run touch vibration.
For the run touch vibration,
there is actually a lot of magic in that.
It is a kind of magic wire, and it is based on a physics engine.
In this, we actually used two worksheets.
The first one is the one that was just introduced by MD.
It is a worksheet for USD.
USD allows us to use the basic physics properties that are used in MD
to create a new kind of work.
In this work, I would like to say that
USD is not a traditional thing.
Because we still need to consider that
in the traditional NRA,
there is a concept of a代理模型 and a渲染模型 in the close calculation.
For example, in the case of代理模型,
if we have something that is attached to the body,
like a bag or a pocket bag,
or something that has a belt,
or something that is decorative,
it actually only needs to be calculated by MD.
Because when we do the physical calculation,
we need a lot of CPU to integrate the human body's model,
and it also needs to be divided into different types.
Therefore,
if we have too much material in the decoding model,
it will greatly affect the efficiency of our CPU.
Then the second task,
we say that we don't need these details,
but we will still reveal them.
Then we will copy it out through the NRA model,
that is, our NRA model,
and then copy it out through OVT.
We can see that
in the front,
we actually found the decoding model,
and when we found the decoding model,
in addition to the decoding clothing model,
we also found a model of the model,
for example,
the model of this model,
I will choose SYNC,
and I will choose SYNC,
including the decoding style,
I will not choose it,
because I only need its decoding model.
At the same time,
this will also greatly improve the efficiency of our work in UAE,
because there are a lot of things in SYNC,
such as in UAE,
every time there is a lot of work in UAE,
it will be very, very slow.
Then after preparing this asset,
next we need to load the run time of UAE,
the close,
close,
set,
such a fork.
In fact,
the traditional,
including UAE 4,
the material modeling engine used in UAE 5,
UAE 5,
is Coex-Close,
which is the first hook on it.
Then later,
from 5.3 to 5.4,
we found that there was a Coex-Close set,
which is the work data flow of this UAE studio.
Then in this,
when we need to connect with ND,
we need to write more of these chapters,
including the following,
some configuration documents of TPU skin,
including,
if we have some students,
especially the work production,
they will use it,
that is,
a little bit,
the production of multiple files
to improve the detail of more text,
text and material,
so at this time,
we also need to open,
that is,
what is this,
the UIS's dynamic data,
the data is added to this file,
and this is what we see,
that is,
in the UAE,
this usd,
this usd is a process of the usd,
and this is the way usd,
or actually,
we will hook,
that is,
we will use,
our on the hard disk,
on the hard disk,
a,
a file that we just imported from mt,
so this file is imported,
and the next step is,
including the post-transmission,
the transmission,
will need some time to come back,
so we,
I am here,
in this virtual environment,
I am adding a,
called,
state matching code,
that is,
the rendering model we just imported,
and then,
we do these two,
merge the action,
and then,
one step by step,
through,
is our,
the naked,
the skin,
the transmission,
the material,
as its initial,
a,
is using,
five actions,
to move,
it's driving,
and then,
in the middle of the game,
we see,
it's some,
it's,
that,
the,
in this,
we can see,
the parameters,
here,
maybe,
not too clear,
these parameters,
are,
that we imported from,
mt,
including,
its gold girl,
and gold girl,
one shoe,
and so on,
then,
in the back of the game,
we know,
There are two most important parts in the sample process.
One is the mass of the raw material in the body
used to control the mass of the raw material in the body.
The other is the mass of the raw material in the body.
We can see that there is a 3D simulation
and 2D simulation interface in the USD interface.
The 2D simulation is completely similar to what we have seen in the ND.
We can directly trace the mass of the raw material in the 3D model
and we can also switch to the 2D version
and modify it in detail.
We know that sometimes it is more convenient to draw some small connections in the 2D model.
After the mass of the raw material is collected,
let's talk about the mass of the raw material.
We know that,
we can use the Madeleine Gauss set of a raw material meshes
to see the mass of the raw material in the body.
In reality, the mass of the raw material is not so precise.
So there are two other ways to normalize it.
The first method is to convert the mass of the raw material
in this way.
We can change the type of mass to Levelset
which will act as the result of multiple審查方式.
Then use this minimum size and the set resolution
to determine whether the amount of value
Of course, in this case, the solution is to add a small number, but in this case, it will help us solve a lot of problems.
Then there is another way, that is, we don't feel these problems, and then we add another process on this side,
that is, we continue to take the body of the character in the game, take it as an IoT level 1, or 2, or 3 corner,
and then make it into a human-to-customized process, and then connect it to the connection configuration,
and then make it into a way that the character's body can be customized.
In this case, this step is actually relatively easy.
We can do this.
In the UI, we can directly convert the character model into an IoT level 1.
If there is an IoT level 1, we can directly convert it into an IoT level 2.
If there is no IoT level 1, we can directly convert the character model into an IoT level 3,
and then convert it into a setting match, and then directly convert it to an IoT level 3.
Then, this is the first way.
It is a way to go from NG to OSD.
The second way is that we can also use the platform interface.
Then we can use the new software in the DCC software,
and then we can also use the new software in the DCC software,
such as Maya, Flash, and so on.
And then the second is that, after entering NG,
we can make it into a relatively-standard design,
a version-based design.
And the third is that, after entering NG,
we can use the 3D GIF, our UG GIF,
and then directly send it to the Error function,
and then then actually make a decision.
After the asset completion is done,
and after entering the UI,
then we put the clothes in different walking bags,
There is a single-layer layout with the MP4, and a double-layer layout with the S-band and double-band.
The third layer is the one we just saw.
The third layer contains the bad side, the internal layer, and the side sub-layer.
That's all I have to say today.
I hope that next time, we can bring some new methods to practice.